<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PowderMills</string>->
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_title">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_checkbox_text">I agree to the terms and conditions</string>
    <string name="continueButtonText">Continue</string>
    <string name="building_list_title_text">PowderMills</string>
    <string name="splash_screen_background">Splash Screen Background</string>
    <string name="history_section_title_text">History</string>
    <string name="function_section_title">Function</string>
    <string name="trivia_section_title">Trivia</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_text">
        [POWDERMILLS APP]TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE1.INTRODUCTION1.1As a user of this Application (“App”) you acknowledge and agree that the use of this App is governed by these terms and conditions of use (the “Terms”). Please read the Terms carefully before using this App as they contain important information about your rightsand obligations. If you have any questions about these Terms please email us at info@powdermills.ie.1.2By accessing and viewing this App you agree that you have read, understood and become bound by the Terms. If you do notwish to be bound by the Terms you may not use this App.  1.3This App is directed solely at users who are at least sixteen (16) years of age and who are located within Ireland at the time of use. 2.DISCLAIMER2.1All material, content and information on this App is for general information purposes only and does not constitute advice.  You shouldnot assume that the content on this App is continuously updated or otherwise contains current and/or accurate information.2.2We do not make any representation or warranty, express or implied, concerning material, content and information on this App, whichare provided “as is”. We exclude all express or implied terms, conditions, warranties, representations or endorsements whatsoever in relationto the viewing, use or performance of this App or any information provided through this App.2.3Your use of this App is at your own risk.  To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we shall not, under any circumstances, beliable to you in contract, tort (including without limitation negligence) or otherwise howsoever for any direct, indirect, incidental, special,punitive or consequential loss that results from your use of or access to, this App or any material, information or content thereon, includingbut not limited to any such loss suffered as a result of our negligence or any inaccuracy, act, error, omission or any other cause and whetheror not on the part of our part or on the part of any other person or entity even if such loss is foreseeable or we have been advised of thepossibility of it.  Without prejudice to the foregoing, we shall not be liable in contract, tort (including without limitation, negligence) orotherwise howsoever to you for any direct or indirect loss of profit, data, opportunity or reputation. 2.4While using this App you shall not:(a)encroach upon or trespass (or attempt to encroach upon or trespass) upon private property; and/or(b)engage in any activity which may cause or result in death or personal injury to you or another individual; and/or©cause damage or nuisance to the property of another personand we shall not be liable in contract, tort (including without limitation, negligence) or otherwise howsoever to you or any other person in theevent that you engage in any of these prohibited activities.2.5The disclaimer in this section 2 shall not operate to exclude any term, warranty or liability that may not be excluded under Irish Law.3.INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY AND MATERIALS3.1We are the owner or the licensee of all intellectual property in this App including but not limited to copyright, moral rights, patents,trademarks, trade names, service marks, designs (software or otherwise), database rights, whether registered or unregistered generally presentand future in and relating to this App (the “Intellectual Property”). This Intellectual Property is protected by copyright laws and treatiesaround the world. All such rights are reserved.4.THIRD PARTY LINKS4.1This App may contain links to other websites or applications.  In no way should this be interpreted as an endorsement of any company,content or products to which this App links. If you decide to access any of third party websites or applications linked to this App, you do soentirely at your own risk. We make no representation or warranty whatsoever about any other website or application which you may accessthrough this App.4.2Please note that third party websites or applications may send their own cookies to users to collect data or solicit personal information,and you are therefore advised to check the terms to use and/or privacy and cookie policies/statements on those third party websites orapplications prior to using them.5.DATA PROTECTION, PRIVACY POLICY5.1We do not collect or store your personal data. 6.GENERAL6.1Law: These Terms shall be governed by, and construed in accordance with, the laws of Ireland and the courts of Ireland shall haveexclusive jurisdiction to settle all disputes that arise out of or in connection with the Terms.6.2Communications: No liability will attach to us in the event of unauthorised access, interference or interception by third parties to thisApp or any of your content or any communication system.53713171
6.3Changes to the Terms: We may, at our discretion and without notice, amend the Terms from time to time, the most recent of whichwill be located on this App.6.4Severability: If the whole or any part of a provision of these Terms is or becomes illegal, invalid or unenforceable, then the provisionso found shall be deemed severable and deleted from them.6.5Assignment: We may, at our discretion assign or transfer any right, title or interest in this App to any successors in title to ourbusinessor to a third party.
    </string>
    <string name="back_button_cd_text">Back Button</string>
    <string name="mapbox_access_token">pk.eyJ1Ijoia2V2aW5tY2dhcnJ5IiwiYSI6ImNraGFoaG56cjFjbnkzMGwybWozeTBlYXMifQ.m_uliyq42bjqqpuMj3dlmA</string>
    <string name="mapbox_style_url">"mapbox://styles/kevinmcgarry/ckhahij881umy19n08trhee74"</string>
    <string name="location_permissions_rationale">Location permissions are required to use the map feature to navigate the park.</string>
    <string name="splash_title_text">Powdermills</string>
    <string name="splash_screen_animation_content_description">Splash screen animated gif of rotating mill.</string>
</resources>